https://tps.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. TPS® Systems will not collect peronally identifiable information about you, unless you provide such information voluntarily. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.
Information We Collect
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.
Our Use of Your Information
We may use information for several general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you’d like to hear about either from us or from our business partners, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research.
You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site’s content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.
Use of Cookies
You also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be collected automatically through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are pieces of information that a website uses to recognize repeated usage, facilitate the users in getting access to and use of the website, and allow usage behavior to be tracked and aggregate data to be compiled to support content improvement and targeted advertising. The use of cookies is standard, and you will find that most websites use them. Most Internet browsers are preset to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet browser to refuse cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used.
Our Disclosure of Your Information
We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.
How You Can Remove Your Information
You may send an email at anytime to sales@tps.com to update or delete personal information or to stop receiving promotional e-mail.
Security
Your information is stored on the TPS® System servers located in the United States. We employ many different security techniques to protect your personal data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company.
Notice
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on the Site.
© 2019. TPS® Systems, Inc. All rights reserved. TPS® is a registered trademark of tps® systems, inc.
